Hudson Hand

Singapore, Singapore mmyroncaldwell@gmail.com

Full Stack Developer with over 5 years of experience building both front-end development and back-end development. Processed knowledge of web applications using AngularJS, React, Vue, Node.js. Key achievement: created an E-commerce that allowed 50k users with 99% accuracy.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full-Stack Developer

HashiCorp, San Francisco, California, Apr 2022 - Apr 2023

- Implemented various private APIs on a Node.js and PostgreSQL back end.
- Contributed as part of a team that made a huge enterprise app for our biggest client, which is being used worldwide by the client's employees. The client's profits increased twofold after one year of using the platform.
- Worked effectively with a remote team spread across three distant corners of the globe.

Front-End Developer

AppDynamics, San Francisco, California, Jan 2020 - Mar 2022

- Implemented React component-based UIs for new product features.
- Completed all complex requirements for forms, including custom form builder widgets.
- Developed a proprietary web application for use in manufacturing processes.
- Built a Google Chrome extension for monitoring and blocking browsing activity.

Front-End Software Engineer

Accenture, South Beach Tower, Singapore, Oct 2017 - Dec 2019

- Maintained site hosting and responded to minor, ongoing client needs.
- Developed a front-end reporting system in Accenture
- Created multiple web tools to use and modify the data in the database.
- Developed and implemented a strategy for migrating the front-end codebase to React additively.

Intern

Accenture, Raffles City Tower, Singapore, June 2017 - Sep 2017

- Experienced the company business work such as Agile methods, morning calls, teamwork and so on.
- Developed and implemented a strategy for migrating the front-end codebase to React additively.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

National University of Singapore, September 2014 – July 2017

SKILLS

- Languages: HTML, CSS, ES6, JavaScript, TypeScript, SQL, PHP, Python
- Frameworks: Angular, Redux, AngularJS, Express.js, Django, Angular Material, Bootstrap, MUI (Material UI)
- Libraries/APIs: React, jQuery, TensorFlow, Node.js, REST APIs, D3.js
- Paradigms: Distributed Programming, REST, Scrum, Agile Software Development, MEAN Stack